Guide to the Diana E. E. Kleiner, Deputy Provost for the Arts, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Diana E. E. Kleiner, deputy provost for the arts, Yale University, records
1989-2003
RU 1011
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.25
(4 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, committee and planning documents, and project and procedure files maintained by Diana E. E. Kleiner as deputy provost for the arts at Yale.
Yale University. Office of the Provost
Kleiner, Diana E. E.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 3-B (YRG 3-B), Records of Yale deputy, associate, and assistant provosts.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the office of the deputy provost, 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, committee and planning documents, and project and procedure files maintained by Diana E. E. Kleiner as deputy provost for the arts at Yale.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Office of the Provost
- Records of the Office of Deputy Provost for the Arts, 1989-2003; Accession 2007-A-023
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  - D.M.C.A.
    - Director, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - Development, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Development IBM, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Classrooms, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Canon, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Arts at Yale University, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Retreat, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Opening, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Development, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Mellon Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Budgets, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Proposals, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Organization, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Re-Organization, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Steering, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - DMCA, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 25 - 27)
    - Salaries, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Subcommittees, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Under Benson, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Committees
    - Advisory
      - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Review, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33 - 35)
    - Review Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Website, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Projects
    - 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Novak Project, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - DivinitySchool
    - Faculty Matters, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Leaves and Procedures, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Dean Search, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Facilities, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Leaves and Procedures, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Stillwater Reports, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Working Group, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Roll Out, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Complaint letters - dean, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 5 Year Plan, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Complaint letters - dean, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Space Relocation 5 Year Plan update, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Leaves and Procedures, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Steering Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 57 - 58)
    - Library, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Instructional Space, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 5 Year Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Demolition Permit, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Dining Halls, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Facilities, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Modified Facilities Plan, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Quad GP. Issues, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Adaptive Reuse Plan, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Construction, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Curriculum Review, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Leaves, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Leaves and Procedures, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Building/Steering, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Berkeley Building Project, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Construction, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Budgets and Salaries, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Budget Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Facilities, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Budget Manager, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Leaves, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Faculty Appointments, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Salary Charts, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Position Authorization, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Accreditation, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Research Fellows, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Deans House, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Leaves and Procedures, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Library, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Guest Housing, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Student Housing, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Divinity Dorms, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - 5 Year Plan, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Business Manager, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Refectory Furniture, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Faculty Appointments, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 99 - 100)
    - Salaries, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - 5 Year Plan, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 102 - 103)
    - Planning Document, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - EPC, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Panoramas, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Board, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - BritishArt Center
    - Search Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Grounds, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - DramaSchool
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Arts Area
    - Website, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Arts Area General Files, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - History of Art: Programming, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Programming, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 120 - 122)
    - Library, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 123 - 124)
  - Committees
    - Arts Area Advisory Committee [2 of 2 only], 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Arts Complex Advisory Group, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Digital Steering Committee
      - Digital Landscape, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 127)
      - Digital Working Group, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Art Gallery
    - Programming, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Architecture
    - Letters, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Stillwater Consulting, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - School, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Programming, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Dean Search, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Building Project, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Undergraduate Major in Architecture, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Appointments [binder], 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Norfolk Summer Program
    - Executive Director, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Trustees, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 145 - 146)
    - Concert Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Collection of Musical Instruments
    - Mellon Development, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Project Advisory Board, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Audio-Visual, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Religious Studies
    - Lutheran Studies Program, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Studies Center, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Philosophy of Religion, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Lutheran Studies Program, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Mormon Conference, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 160)